this is the time known as the great pirate era a countless array of pirates go to battle across
the seas in search of the one piece the legendary treasure left behind by gold roger king of the
pirates monkey d luffy a boy whose body turned to rubber after eating the gum gum fruit set sail
to become the next king of the pirates as luffy and his crew conquer numerous obstacles they
capture the unwanted attention of the world government which will use any means necessary
to stop them now this is sight i can't wait to see what kind of adventures up next with a charted
course awash in danger and intrigue the crew will cut a path across the grand line to the new world
amidst the fire overtaking gray terminal ace and adan faced blue jam while an injured luffy
was taken back to mount corvo elsewhere the goa kingdom welcomed a celestial dragon however the
world noble was displeased to see sabo's ship in his path and open fire
take good care of him a letter from the brother
get out of my way i gotta find eggs easy luffy easy i know how you feel but it's still too dangerous
you got banged up pretty bad and the place is crawling with soldiers who cares please come down and listen
to me we get it we're scared too but right now we just need to have faith that the boss and ace are still
alive dogger went back to look for him so be patient understand this is hard on everyone okay
the fishing boat has been hit what happened to the child that kid shouldn't have gotten in the
celestial dragon's way get out of there damn why'd he shoot at me
say john like there's a child on that ship anyone who flies a black flag is a filthy pirate his age is
irrelevant he must pay
come on a commoner should know better don't cross my ship you stupid pirate brat
what why would they fire on that ship a second time who cares we don't want to make the celestial
dragon man this is an important ceremony let him do whatever he wants oh clear the wreckage already
hey i got news ace and the boss are what is it they came back
they both made it
i was so scared she's badly wounded get them both in
inside now hurry hang in there boss
get off
come on did you seriously think i was dead
baby quit crying already
i'm standing right in front of you dummy
come on ace take it easy on the kiddo for once
luffy's just happy to see you
what happened the night of the fire we all came back here with luffy so we haven't heard a word
can you tell us everything that happened to you and the boss
oh well um we fought blue jam
ah
we barely defeated him
whoa whoa whoa hey dadan are you all right
we made it through the fire
dadan was suffering from some serious burns though
eventually we managed to get to the riverside in the in-between forest
stay with me dadan you can't die
see
you can't do that
stop
i went into town to steal medicine and grab whatever food i could find
i'm no doctor but i did what i could to save to don's life
ah
quit worrying about me ace
please
just go
cut the crap
it's your responsibility to take me home remember
and you're still gonna do it while i make sure you don't die
hear that
keep your ears to the ground
some survivors could be lurking around here
don't let anyone get away
stuff them out
yes sir
what an ordeal
in any case all that matters is that both of you are back safe
i'm sorry
i made you worry
that fire was huge and they were hunting down survivors
Sabo must think we're dead right now
this kingdom's likely full of lowly plebeians that will get in my way
be on the lookout for any disruption
right
i wonder what Sabo's been up to
but at least ace finally made it back right
he even carried to don home with them
ace
when i came for you
i'm staying
i won't run
why
did you do that
i don't know
i can't help but get fired up
i'm afraid if i run
that i might leave something important behind me
so i fight
luffy was there
so i had no choice
it's tough to explain
but i think that's why
even when he faced a wave of far more powerful enemies
roger would never think of running away
did that fool have a death wish running away is a strategy too
for him it wasn't even an option
think about it
retreat means leaving people behind
if roger ran
he'd be abandoning his crew the people he loved most
so when you think about it
it's not that he wouldn't run
rather he made sure the enemy couldn't go after his crew
he always protected them
he was a different kind of animal in times like those
he once wrecked a whole country's army
because some soldiers decided to mouth off about his men
when he was angry roger would get violent
he was selfish and short-tempered
but he wore his heart on his sleeve
he was like a boy that never grew up
for better or worse his childhood was a lot like aces
the pain he went through just made him hold on tighter to the ones he loved
roger could be a very reckless man
but he lived to become king of the pirates
no easy feat
despite his flaws and his bad reputation
his crew still trusted him completely
sure i may be a marine
but even i can't help respecting him
that's why i decided to take care of ace
i'm the one taking care of him you ass
do you got something you want to say to me
no never mind
people all over the world still hate roger
and even though ace holds a grudge against him too
they really are like father like son
all right wonder who's gonna win
dogra
you went to town to look for ace into dawn right
surprise they came back home already
oh did they really that's just great perfect
what sabo
that can't be
you're lying to me dammit
why would you even joke about that kind of thing
take it easy
i told you exactly what i saw i swear
i know how you feel everything happened so fast i could hardly believe it
it felt like a nightmare but i know that was sabo
shut up we watched him go back with his dad to their home in high town
you can't have seen him out at sea by himself
that's right
sabo is with his family
bandits like us know how he feels
we know what it means to be turned away from your home
to be free
sabo didn't want to be a noble
if he was truly happy he wouldn't have gone out to sea
and the sabo i saw wasn't just failing away from his family he was flying a jolly roger
we shouldn't have let him go it's all our fault
even if i had parents i was still alone
sabo why didn't we go back into town and bring him back here
we're so stupid
tell me where i could find the bastard that killed him
i'm gonna beat him to death with my bare hands
you can't kill a celestial dragon that's impossible
i'll make him pay
hold on ace
enough of that you little punk
you think you're so tough when you're really just a cocky stubborn little brat
what can you do against a world noble you think he's just some thug
you're just some no-name kid
you'll die and nobody will give a crap
swept under the rug the very next day
it was this whole rotten country that killed sabo
this rotten world
what can a scrawny brat like you do about it
your father on the other hand changed the world with his death
when you become a man as important as him
then and only then can you take revenge
tie this fool up
yes ma'am
sabo
dammit
shut up luffy quit crying like a girl or else i'll
no
oh
You've come to your senses now, I hope.
Guys, untie him.
Right.
Try to keep your cool, okay?
Where's Luffy?
He was crying all night.
Finally fell asleep.
Oh, my gosh.
You're not going to believe this.
We got a letter.
It's from Sabo.
He must have sent it before he left.
Look, I think it's really from him.
Give it.
Don't worry.
I won't head to town.
It's for Luffy and me, isn't it?
Ace, Luffy, I hope you guys weren't hurt in the fire.
I'm worried about you both, but something tells me you're okay.
I've got a surprise to tell you.
By the time you get this letter, I'll be long gone.
That's right.
I'm heading out to sea.
One thing led to another, and I decided to set out before you two.
I don't know where I'm going yet, but I do know that anywhere will be better than this place.
And don't worry, I haven't given up on my dream.
I'm still going to be a pirate.
I got a head start, but I'm sure you'll catch up in no time.
When we meet again, we'll be unstoppable.
We'll have our reunion on the Grand Line.
Three pirate captains more free than the wind.
By the way, Ace, I'm curious.
Which one of us do you think is the real big brother?
Anyway, wherever we sail, we'll always have our brotherhood.
It may sound kind of cheesy, but that bond is what I treasure most in this world.
Luffy is still weak.
And a crybaby.
Who knows if he'll ever grow out of that.
But he's still our little brother.
So please take good care of him.
They call this journalism?
The hell do I care about some world noble partying?
Surprise, surprise.
Nobody's covered Sabo yet.
Yeah, I heard his parents didn't do a thing.
It's iffy.
They may be nobles, but even high-ranking nobles are powerless against the world government and celestial dragons.
How's Luffy doing?
Is he any better?
Well, he hasn't been eating much.
But he still eats twice as much as we do.
Sabo's death must have really gotten to him.
Ace, Luffy, listen.
The three of us, we're going to leave this country.
We're going to sail the seas and see the whole world.
From now on, we're honest-to-goodness brothers.
Cheers to that.
Brothers!
How long are you going to lay there like a moron?
By the way, the treasure we were keeping in the forest is gone.
Someone must have gotten to it.
Survivors from Blue Jam's crew might have taken it.
Or maybe the military.
Either way, there's nothing we can do at this point.
Meh.
I don't care about the treasure.
Not anymore.
I mean, those were pirate savings I was sharing with Sabo.
And you too later on, I guess.
But in the end, he didn't need money to set sail.
So why should I get bent out of shape about it?
After all, what's the point in having treasure if you can't even protect it?
I...
Hey, Ace...
I want to get stronger.
Stronger...
And stronger and stronger...
And stronger and stronger.
Stronger and stronger.
Stronger and stronger and stronger and stronger.
And stronger and stronger.
I want to be the strongest in the world.
And then, I'll protect everyone.
I won't lose anyone I care about.
You gotta make me a promise.
I'm begging you.
Please don't die, Gaze!
Cut it out.
You ought to be worried about dying before I do.
What, did you forget you're a lot weaker than me?
Listen, and you listen up good.
I'm never going to die.
You know, Sabo told me to take care of you.
So I promise, I'm not gonna die, okay? Not ever.
At least not as long as I've got a wussy little brother who needs me to protect him.
Yeah, okay.
Smarts aren't exactly my strong point.
So, I still don't really understand why Sabo was killed.
But whoever did it, they must be opposed to freedom.
Because they shot him down before he ever got a taste of it.
But we shared that same cup of sake with him and we're still alive.
Luffy, listen to me, okay?
There's just one way to live.
And that's without any regrets.
Boys from families like mine?
Once they turn 18, they're officially registered as nobles.
That's why I'm leaving.
I gotta be gone before I'm 17.
Someday, we're gonna set sail just like Sabo.
We're gonna live the way we wanna live.
More free than anyone else.
But you know what that means.
We'll make plenty of enemies along the way.
We're gonna have to fight Garp someday, I bet.
We gotta be willing to risk everything.
Let's go out to sea at 17, just like Sabo planned.
Then, we'll be pirates.
We're pirates.
Luffy and Ace bury their sorrow and grow stronger day after day as they train to be pirates.
As time marches on, they soon bid farewell to their childhood home and take to the sea at last.
In hopes of achieving the dream that Sabo could not.
On the next, One Piece, to live up to the promise, departures of their own, I'm gonna be king of the pirates!